Tyler Posadovsky

22 Speers Crescent Kanata, ON K2M 1V9

January 15, 2016

Dear Hiring Manager,

I am writing with regards to your job posting on myCo-op. I believe I would be a good candidate for the position because I have the technical skills required to excel at it, as well as many other transferable skills that I believe will help me quickly adapt to the work environment.

Throughout my studies at Carleton University, as well as on my own personal schedule, I have come extremely proficient in the entire Adobe Creative Suite. My experience with these applications have allowed me to excel in my many design projects. (I have utilized)I gained strong Photoshop skills in my Graphic Design course at Carleton, where I used Photoshop to create commercial-quality advertisements, and create design mockups for modernized user-friendly websites. I designed a website to showcase my portfolio. Not only can I code and style a website with ease, but I also have exceptional knowledge in friendly user interface design, and I always apply this to my websites. I am also very experienced in several coding languages, such as C++, Java and Python. In my programming course at Carleton, I successfully coded a game where the player could move around collecting points, and avoiding enemies, while detecting different ground levels throughout the game map. I also have experience in creating databases, and storing information them. I am also an expert with all of the Microsoft Office applications, including Word, Excel and Powerpoint. Aside from my technical skills, I am also a fast learner, amazing problem solver and strong communicator, and I take extreme pride and dedication in my work.

I want to work for this company because I would love to be able to share my ideas, talents and values with a growing company that promotes originality and nobility. I believe I am a great fit for the position because I am a natural born designer and innovator, and I am very good at implementing my designs and creativity to create user-friendly, cutting-edge designs. I would be motivated to not only do well at the position, but to go above and beyond what you would expect.

	•		111 16	
Ihank	VALLETAY VALLE	consideration	and I look torward	l to hearing from vou.

Sincerely,

Tyler Posadovsky

Tyler Posadovsky

22 Speers Crescent Kanata, ON, K2M 1V9

(613) 435-4045, <u>typosadovsky@rogers.com</u>, <u>www.typosadovsky.com</u> https://ca.linkedin.com/in/ty-posadovsky-841b4a112

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information Technology

2014 - Present

Interactive Multimedia and Design, Co-op Option

Carleton University, Ottawa, Ontario

- 2nd Year, 10.0/12.0 CGPA, A-
- Scholarships: Murdoch Maxwell MacOdrum Scholarship
- Expected graduation date: April 2018

AVAILABILITY

Available for 4 months starting May 2016

RELEVENT SKILLS, EXPERIENCES AND ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Technical Skills

- Designed a website mockup which required me to use many of the Adobe Suite, which helped me strengthen my skill with the entire Adobe Suite
- Designed my own website for a theoretical teleporting device which allowed me to become extremely proficient with HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Experienced in several programming languages including C language, and Java
- Created a 2D platforming game using C++ and Allegro library to help solidify my understanding of Object Oriented Programming
- Created a cooking recipe database using SQL and PHP which allowed me to gain an understanding on the functionality of databases and how to create and monitor them

Design Skills

 Designed a CD album cover for Distakore Music using Photoshop which expanded my ability to create attractive graphic design projects using layers and various Photoshop effects

- Created several 3D action animations using Maya which allowed me to gain experience in 3D modelling and animation
- Directed, filmed and edited my own Doritos commercial using Premiere which allowed me to professionalize my video editing skills

Communication Skills

- Wrote and performed a speech about a drug awareness program to an entire school which raised my confidence as a speaker in front of crowds
- Integrated many word spreadsheets, Powerpoint presentations and word documents into many educational assignments which has mastered my proficiency in the entire Microsoft Office collection
- Redesigned and presented a parking machine to my peers which allowed me to improve my presentation skills to efficiently get across relevant information in a time limit situation

APPLIED PROJECTS

Website Design Project

September 2015 – October 2015

My Portfolio Website

• Designed a website to showcase my design projects over the year which helped me become comfortable

with using HTML, CSS and JavaScript proficiently

• Put my website on Github which allowed me to gain a better knowledge of the git source code managing system and how to relink a website on the Github server to a new URL that you create

Cartoon Animation

July 2015 - Present

The Jacobson's Cartoon Series

- Invented my own cartoon series and designed all the characters, and performed the animations, which allowed me to facilitate my ability to construct convincing and entertaining animations
- Developed the stories and concepts for the cartoon series, improving my creative qualities for creating entertaining animations for an audience

3D Modelling Project

April 2015 - Present

Superhero Character Design

- Designed and modelled my own superhero characters using Maya, which allowed me to implement my artistic skills into a 3D atmosphere
- Integrated a rigging system within my models using Maya to allow the capability of animating my character models

2D and 3D Level Design

April 2015 – Present

Video Game Level Designs

- Conceptualized 3D height maps using Maya which strengthened my understanding of 3-Dimensional surfaces and how to implement them into user-friendly levels
- Implemented my knowledge of C++ language and the Allegro library to build a user friendly 2D platforming map, and coded the height response to the location of the player

WORK EXPERIENCE

Cashier/Customer Service

April 2015 - present

Superstore, Kanata, ON

- Delivered fast, efficient service to continuous waves of customers, which helped improved my ability to work efficiently in fast-paced stressful environments
- Adapted quickly to my duties as a cashier and quickly progressed to customer service, which taught me how to learn quickly and adjust efficiently to knew environments and situations

Team Member/Shift Lead Coordinator

November 2012 – April 2015

Landmark Cinemas, Kanata, ON

- Responded quickly and efficiently to problems on the job, greatly improving my ability to identify and perform the required actions to solve the problem
- Coordinated shift procedures and lead other team members to do their duties in a team-based environment, which strengthened my leadership qualities and coordination skills